ARINZE PETER CHINEDU

WEB DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I am an adaptable professional developer with 4+ years of experience and a proven knowledge in blending art of design with skill of programming, real time data, and web design to deliver engaging user experience through efficient website development, proactive feature optimization, and relentless debugging. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the software development role in your company.

EDUCATION

January 2015 - September 2019. Nnamdi Azikiwe University. Awka, Nigeria.

Bachelor of Science, computer Science. Honors: cum laude (GPA: 4.5/5.0).

CONTACT

Phone: (+234) 903-280-6278

Skype: https://join.skype.com/invite/HfuVGUMZNaQm

Email: breezeconcept3@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/Mr-IRobot/

My Website: https://github.com/Mr-IRobot/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/breeze-s-concept-578a6b1b5

SOME WORK REFERENCE:

Portfolio website: www.johnchibuzz.com

Affiliate marketing website: www.kliqaffiliate.com

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Python
- Diango
- Sqlite3
- ◆ HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
 - ReactUi/Ux
- Photoshop
- ❖ Git & Github
 - Heroku
 - Wordpress
 - ❖ PHP
 - Laravel
 - MySQL

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

SEP 2019 - Present

BREEZE CONCEPT, AWKA, NIGERIA.

- Managed a small scale firm that offers services to businesses and individuals
- The services include; web development (android/iOS), software development, branding, Ui/Ux, video editing, photo editing/manipulation and photo arts.
- We help these businesses to scale up by providing an online presence for their products and services.

SEP 2019 - Present

Frontend web developer Breeze concept, Awka, Nigeria.

- Developed landing pages, dashboards and online applications using HTML/CSS, Bootstrap and Javascript.
- Developed designs to meet specific requirements such as quickloading sites with particular.

CERTIFICATION

September 2019
BSc in Computer science and programming
Nnamdi Azikiwe University

September 2021 - January 2022 Backend web developer KLIQ, Lagos, Nigeria.

 Developed an e-commerce website that uses data analytics to visualize the data on products available and showcases a statistical report on the data.